<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">

    //tps error string
    <string name="ECI999"/>
    <string name="ECI223"/>
    <string name="ECI436">%1$d</string>
    <string name="ECI601"/>
    <string name="ECI067"/>
    <string name="ECI602"/>
    <string name="ECI188"/>
    <string name="ECI600">Choose order to confirm (ECI600)</string>
    <string name="ECI535_1">%1$s</string>
    <string name="ECI840"/>
    <string name="ECI841"/>
    <string name="ECI842"/>
    <string name="ECI843"/>
    <string name="ECI844"/>
    <string name="ECI929"/>
    //tps error string end
    <string name="ECI063_1">Cannot connect to server (ECI063).\n%1$s</string>

    <string name="ECS2">An error occurs in processing. Please contact to Trading Department (ECS002).</string>
    <string name="ECS260">The amount transferred is less than %1$s VND(ECS260).</string>
    <string name="ECS261">The amount transferred is larger than %1$s VND(ECS261).</string>
    <string name="ECS633">The customer does not have permission to view market insight (ECS633)</string>
    <string name="ECS634">The customer does not have delegate permission to view market insight (ECS634)</string>
    <string name="ECS635">The password and PIN code must be difference (ECS635)</string>
    <string name="ECS647">Can not change order because its Qty is difference lots (ECS647)</string>
    <string name="ECS703">The price step is incorrect (ECS703)</string>
    <string name="ECS749">You do not have permission to access streaming data (ECS749)</string>
    <string name="ECS763">Temporary system issue. Please try again later. (ECS763)</string>
    <string name="ECS035">The account was existed (ECS035).</string>
    <string name="ECS036">The agent is not exist (ECS036).</string>
    <string name="ECS10">Can not change password (ECS010).</string>
    <string name="ECS1000">Invalid mobile phone number (ECS1000).</string>
    <string name="ECS1001">This mobile phone number was registered by another account (ECS1001).</string>
    <string name="ECS1002">Invalid CCPin (ECS1002).</string>
    <string name="ECS1003"> The mobile phone number can not be empty while you chose authentication by mobile number (ECS1003).</string>
    <string name="ECS1004">Can not unregister CC information (ECS1004).</string>
    <string name="ECS1005">This customer ID has already registered in Contact Center (ECS1005).</string>
    <string name="ECS1006">This customer ID is not a agency ID (ECS1006).</string>
    <string name="ECS1007">This customer ID is not managed by this agency (ECS1007).</string>
    <string name="ECS1008">You are not allowed to change this account’s CCPIN (ECS1008).</string>
    <string name="ECS1009">Your request was existed (ECS1009).</string>
    <string name="ECS1010">Confirmation code is invalid (ECS1010)</string>
    <string name="ECS1011">Confirmation code has expired (ECS1011).</string>
    <string name="ECS1036">You have to deselect notify channel in OTP confirmcode service before you destroy all registering devices (ECS1036)</string>
    <string name="ECS1048">You do not have permission to active account (ECS1048)</string>
    <string name="ECS1049">You do not have permission to money transfer external (ECS1049)</string>
    <string name="ECS11">Can not create account (ECS011).</string>
    <string name="ECS12">This account is locked (ECS012).</string>
    <string name="ECS13">An error occurs in delivery your order. Please place order again (ECS013).</string>
    <string name="ECS14">This order is not  allowed to cancel (ECS014).</string>
    <string name="ECS15">This order is not allowed to change (ECS015).</string>
    <string name="ECS150">Order is valid (ECS150).</string>
    <string name="ECS151">The market is closed. (ECS151).</string>
    <string name="ECS152">Price is incorrect. (ECS152).</string>
    <string name="ECS153">It is incorrect for buy/sell type (ECS153).</string>
    <string name="ECS154">The exchange market doesn’t allow placing the contrary orders of the same stock at ATO or ATC session (ECS154).</string>
    <string name="ECS155">The stock symbol is not exist (ECS155).</string>
    <string name="ECS156">This stock symbol is  halted (ECS156).</string>
    <string name="ECS157">Bond trading is not allowed (ECS157).</string>
    <string name="ECS158">The Qty is invalid (ECS158).</string>
    <string name="ECS159">The Qty can not over 500,000 (ECS159).</string>
    <string name="ECS16">The confirmation code is incorrect (ECS016).</string>
    <string name="ECS160">Price step is invalid (ECS160).</string>
    <string name="ECS161">The price is not lower than floor price (ECS161).</string>
    <string name="ECS162">The price is not greater than ceiling price (ECS162).</string>
    <string name="ECS163">Not enough room for foreigner to buy (ECS163).</string>
    <string name="ECS164">Not enough money or power purchase for buying (ECS164).</string>
    <string name="ECS165">Not enough stock for selling (ECS165).</string>
    <string name="ECS166">You don\'t have this stock (ECS166).</string>
    <string name="ECS167">Not enough stock Qty in your account (ECS167).</string>
    <string name="ECS168">This confirmation link is expired (ECS168).</string>
    <string name="ECS169">This confirmation is confirmed (ECS169).</string>
    <string name="ECS17">An error occurs in delivery your order. Please place order again (ECS017).</string>
    <string name="ECS170">This account can not buy stock. Please check your CAN BUY capability in Account Information screen (ECS170).</string>
    <string name="ECS171">This account can not sell stock. Please check your CAN SELL capability in Account Information screen (ECS171).</string>
    <string name="ECS172">Cannot cancel the matched order (ECS172).</string>
    <string name="ECS173">Cannot get cash balance from back-office (ECS173).</string>
    <string name="ECS174">Cannot get stock balance from back-office (ECS174).</string>
    <string name="ECS175">Incorrect confirmation code (ECS175).</string>
    <string name="ECS176">Not reach time to receive order. (ECS176).</string>
    <string name="ECS177">Invalid account (ECS177).</string>
    <string name="ECS178">Price is incorrect: It is multiply by 100 for HNX stock (ECS178).</string>
    <string name="ECS179">Price is incorrect: It is multiply by 100 for HOSE stock (in case Price  50,000) (ECS179).</string>
    <string name="ECS18">This cardID or passport is existed (ECS018).</string>
    <string name="ECS180">Price is incorrect: It is multiply by 500 for HOSE stock (in case 50,000 =Price 100,000) (ECS180).</string>
    <string name="ECS181">Price is incorrect: It is multiply by 1,000 for HOSE stock (in case Price = 100,000) (ECS181).</string>
    <string name="ECS182">Price is incorrect: No ATO, ATC for HNX market (ECS182).</string>
    <string name="ECS183">Price is incorrect: ATO is only valid in Ready ATO Session (ECS183).</string>
    <string name="ECS184">Price is incorrect: ATC is only valid in ATC Session (ECS184).</string>
    <string name="ECS185">Your Account Information (STC Code, PC Flag) is not matched. Please contact with our Online Trading Department for support. (ECS185).</string>
    <string name="ECS186">This channel is not configured to place order, please notify to our Online Trading Department to fix it (ECS186).</string>
    <string name="ECS187">You do not have enough cash for advance (ECS187).</string>
    <string name="ECS188">Do not allow to advance cash in due date (ECS188).</string>
    <string name="ECS189">Cash advance  is less than or equal to 0 (ECS189).</string>
    <string name="ECS19">This account is locked (ECS019).</string>
    <string name="ECS190">You don\'t have trading permission on Online Trading system. Please contact with our Online Trading Department for support (ECS190).</string>
    <string name="ECS191">Incorrect market (ECS191).</string>
    <string name="ECS192">This stock have not order on this session (ECS192).</string>
    <string name="ECS193">Price is incorrect: No ATO, ATC or MP for UPCOM market (ECS193).</string>
    <string name="ECS194">Price is incorrect: It is multiply by 100 for UPCOM stock (ECS194).</string>
    <string name="ECS195">You can not cancel orders that have order id is  zero. Please contact to Online Trading Department for support (ECS195).</string>
    <string name="ECS196">You do not allow to set order in break time of lunch (ECS196).</string>
    <string name="ECS197">Can not cash advance in holiday (ECS197).</string>
    <string name="ECS198">Do not allow place MP order in this time (ECS198).</string>
    <string name="ECS199">Do not delegate permission to do this feature (ECS199).</string>
    <string name="ECS20">Input error (ECS020).</string>
    <string name="ECS200">The order number incorrect (ECS200).</string>
    <string name="ECS201">Cannot cancel the cancelled order (ECS201).</string>
    <string name="ECS202">Do not allow cancel the order from other channels (ECS202).</string>
    <string name="ECS203">Not allow to cancel this order in this session (ECS203).</string>
    <string name="ECS204">Not allow to cancel HNX order (ECS204).</string>
    <string name="ECS205">Incorrect account (ECS205).</string>
    <string name="ECS206">Unidentified error (ECS206).</string>
    <string name="ECS207">This account is being used in a different computer/device or you have not logged out your account from the previous login (ECS207).</string>
    <string name="ECS208">Token code is incorrect (ECS208).</string>
    <string name="ECS209">The token code is expired (ECS209).</string>
    <string name="ECS21">Your advance withdraw request is being processed, can not cancel (ECS021).</string>
    <string name="ECS210">Token license is expired (ECS210).</string>
    <string name="ECS211">Token code is incorrect (ECS211).</string>
    <string name="ECS212">This token is locked (ECS212).</string>
    <string name="ECS213">This token is not activated with your account (ECS213).</string>
    <string name="ECS214">The token is out of synchronous (ECS214).</string>
    <string name="ECS215">Can not connect to the authentication server (ECS215).</string>
    <string name="ECS216">Token code is incorrect (ECS216).</string>
    <string name="ECS217">Receiver\'s name is invalid (ECS217).</string>
    <string name="ECS218">Receiver\'s bank account is invalid (ECS218).</string>
    <string name="ECS219">You can not cancel cash transfer order processing (ECS219).</string>
    <string name="ECS22">Your advance withdraw request is completed, can not cancel (ECS022).</string>
    <string name="ECS220">You can not cancel cash transfer order processed (ECS220).</string>
    <string name="ECS221">You can not cancel cash transfer order rejected (ECS221).</string>
    <string name="ECS222">You can not cancel cash transfer order cancelled (ECS222).</string>
    <string name="ECS223">Your contract number is invalid (ECS223).</string>
    <string name="ECS224">Your net advance can not less than advance fee (ECS224).</string>
    <string name="ECS225">You can not transfer money more than you have (ECS225).</string>
    <string name="ECS226">You do not have permission for buying in this account (ECS226)</string>
    <string name="ECS227">You do not have permission for selling in this account (ECS227)</string>
    <string name="ECS228">You do not have permission for canceling in this account (ECS228)</string>
    <string name="ECS229">You do not have permission for requesting cash advance in this account (ECS229)</string>
    <string name="ECS23">Your advance withdraw request is refused, can not cancel (ECS023).</string>
    <string name="ECS230">You do not have permission for requesting money transfer in this account (ECS230).</string>
    <string name="ECS231">You do not have permission for viewing balance in this account (ECS231).</string>
    <string name="ECS232">You do not have permission for viewing history in this account (ECS232).</string>
    <string name="ECS233">You do not have permission for viewing transactions in this account (ECS233).</string>
    <string name="ECS234">You do not have permission for viewing account information in this account (ECS234).</string>
    <string name="ECS235">Can not register for odd-slot selling. We do not buy at this time. (ECS235).</string>
    <string name="ECS236">Can not cancel the processing deal (ECS236).</string>
    <string name="ECS237">Can not cancel the processed deal (ECS237).</string>
    <string name="ECS238">Can not cancel the rejected deal (ECS238).</string>
    <string name="ECS239">Can not cancel the cancelled deal (ECS239).</string>
    <string name="ECS24">Your advance withdraw request is cancelled, can not cancel (ECS024).</string>
    <string name="ECS240">Can not cancel the processing deal (ECS240).</string>
    <string name="ECS241">Can not cancel the processed deal (ECS241).</string>
    <string name="ECS242">Can not cancel the rejected deal (ECS242).</string>
    <string name="ECS243">Can not cancel the cancelled deal (ECS243).</string>
    <string name="ECS244">Can not cancel the inactive account (ECS244).</string>
    <string name="ECS245">Can not lock the inactive account (ECS245).</string>
    <string name="ECS246">Invalid contract number of stock transfer (ECS246).</string>
    <string name="ECS247">Can not cancel the processing deal (ECS247).</string>
    <string name="ECS248">Can not cancel the rejected deal (ECS248).</string>
    <string name="ECS249">Can not cancel the processed deal (ECS249).</string>
    <string name="ECS25">It is overtime or break time to make cash advance for withdraw (ECS025).</string>
    <string name="ECS250">Can not cancel the cancelled deal (ECS250).</string>
    <string name="ECS251">Can not do cash advance with margin account (ECS251).</string>
    <string name="ECS252">Authentication failed (ECS252).</string>
    <string name="ECS257">Can not register for registered deal on pending (ECS257).</string>
    <string name="ECS258">Can not register for registered deal on processed (ECS258).</string>
    <string name="ECS259">Can not register for registered deal on processing (ECS259).</string>
    <string name="ECS26">Available time for cash advance requests is from %1$s to %2$s every trading day or out of service time/breaking time (ECS026).</string>
    <string name="ECS262">Can not enter night order in this session (ECS262).</string>
    <string name="ECS263">Buy limitation for this stock is not enough (ECS263).</string>
    <string name="ECS264">Not support MP order (ECS264).</string>
    <string name="ECS265">Not allow new right registration in this time (ECS265).</string>
    <string name="ECS266">Not allow refuse right registration in this status (ECS266).</string>
    <string name="ECS267">You do not have authorization to view status and history cash advance (ECS267).</string>
    <string name="ECS268">You do not have authorization to view status and history money transfer (ECS268).</string>
    <string name="ECS269">You do not have authorization to view cash transaction (ECS269).</string>
    <string name="ECS27">You should change your emergency password (ECS027).</string>
    <string name="ECS270">You do not have authorization to view cash transaction (ECS270).</string>
    <string name="ECS271">You do not have authorization to edit information (ECS271).</string>
    <string name="ECS272">You do not have authorization to view status and history rigister right (ECS272).</string>
    <string name="ECS273">You do not have authorization to eidt or cancel or reject register right (ECS273).</string>
    <string name="ECS274">You do not have authorization to view status and history sell odd-lot (ECS274).</string>
    <string name="ECS275">You do not have authorization to eidt or cancel or reject sell odd-lot (ECS275).</string>
    <string name="ECS276">You do not have authorization to view status night order (ECS276).</string>
    <string name="ECS277">You do not have authorization to order buy or sell or cancel night order (ECS277).</string>
    <string name="ECS278">You do not have authorization to view condition order (ECS278).</string>
    <string name="ECS279">You do not have authorization to order buy or sell or cancel condition order (ECS279).</string>
    <string name="ECS28">This system have not been licensed (ECS028).</string>
    <string name="ECS280">You do not have permission to view stock balance (ECS280).</string>
    <string name="ECS281">You do not have permission to view cash balance (ECS281).</string>
    <string name="ECS282">You do not have permission to view order history (ECS282).</string>
    <string name="ECS283">You do not have permission to view stock transaction (ECS283).</string>
    <string name="ECS284">You do not have permission to view cash transaction (ECS284).</string>
    <string name="ECS285">You do not have permission to view order status (ECS285).</string>
    <string name="ECS286">You do not have permission to view account information (ECS286).</string>
    <string name="ECS287">You do not have permission to change account information (ECS287).</string>
    <string name="ECS288">You do not have permission to view status and history cash advance (ECS288).</string>
    <string name="ECS289">You do not have permission to edit or cancel  order cash advance (ECS289).</string>
    <string name="ECS29">This system have not been authenticated (ECS029).</string>
    <string name="ECS290">You do not have permission to view status or history money transfer (ECS290).</string>
    <string name="ECS291">You do not have permission to edit or cancel order money transfer (ECS291).</string>
    <string name="ECS292">You do not have permission to view status or history of right registration (ECS292).</string>
    <string name="ECS293">You do not have permission to edit or cancel the right registration(ECS293).</string>
    <string name="ECS294">You do not have permission to view status or history sell odd-lot (ECS294).</string>
    <string name="ECS295">You do not have permission to edit or cancel sell odd-lot (ECS295).</string>
    <string name="ECS296">You do not have permission to view night order (ECS296).</string>
    <string name="ECS297">You do not have permission to change sell or buy or cancel night order (ECS297).</string>
    <string name="ECS298">You do not have permission to view condition order (ECS298).</string>
    <string name="ECS299">You do not have permission to change sell or buy or cancel condition order (ECS299).</string>
    <string name="ECS3">The account or password or captcha is invalid (ECS003/ECS500/ECS718).</string>
    <string name="ECS30">You have been logged out because you logged in on a different computer or device (ECS030).</string>
    <string name="ECS300">You don\'t enough cash for right registration (ECS300).</string>
    <string name="ECS301">Effective date must smaller than current date (ECS301).</string>
    <string name="ECS302">Error: can not insert into database (ECS302).</string>
    <string name="ECS303">Incorrect matching type (ECS303).</string>
    <string name="ECS304">Incorrect warning type (ECS304).</string>
    <string name="ECS305">Incorrect trailing type (ECS305).</string>
    <string name="ECS306">Incorrect alert type (ECS306).</string>
    <string name="ECS307">You do not have permission to view this function (ECS307).</string>
    <string name="ECS308">You do not have permission to update this function (ECS308).</string>
    <string name="ECS309">This notifier is existed (ECS309).</string>
    <string name="ECS31">The requested advance withdraw amount is over (ECS031).</string>
    <string name="ECS310">Notify type is invalid (ECS310).</string>
    <string name="ECS311">This notify setting is existed  (ECS311).</string>
    <string name="ECS312">You do not have permission to view this function(ECS312).</string>
    <string name="ECS313">You do not have permission to update this function (ECS313).</string>
    <string name="ECS314">Error cannot new money transfer for foreign account (ECS314).</string>
    <string name="ECS315">You did not agree on Online Trading Agreement (ECS315).</string>
    <string name="ECS316">You do not have authorization to view notifier (ECS316).</string>
    <string name="ECS317">You do not have authorization to change notifier (ECS317).</string>
    <string name="ECS318">You do not have authorization to view notifier setting (ECS318).</string>
    <string name="ECS319">You do not have authorization to change notifier setting (ECS319).</string>
    <string name="ECS32">You should change your password (ECS032).</string>
    <string name="ECS320">Do not have permission for viewing realized gain/loss (ECS320).</string>
    <string name="ECS321"> Do hot have authorized permission for viewing realized gain/loss (ECS321).</string>
    <string name="ECS322">You do not have not permission to view stock transferation in this account (ECS322).</string>
    <string name="ECS323">You do not have permission to view stock transferation  (ECS323).</string>
    <string name="ECS324">You do not have permission to create new  stock transferation  in this account (ECS324).</string>
    <string name="ECS325">You do not have permission to create new stock transferation  (ECS325).</string>
    <string name="ECS326">Can not transfer stock to the same account (ECS326).</string>
    <string name="ECS327">Incorrect receiver account (ECS327).</string>
    <string name="ECS328">Incorrect contract number (ECS328).</string>
    <string name="ECS329">You do not have permission to view stock balance  in this account (ECS329).</string>
    <string name="ECS33">You should change your PIN code (ECS033).</string>
    <string name="ECS330">You do not have authorization for trading (ECS330).</string>
    <string name="ECS331">Your default account is not actived  (ECS331).</string>
    <string name="ECS332">You can not cancel the waiting for canceling deal (ECS332).</string>
    <string name="ECS333">You can not cancel the cancelled deal (ECS333).</string>
    <string name="ECS334">You can not transfer odd-slot stocks (ECS334).</string>
    <string name="ECS335">You can not trade UPCOM stocks with margin account (ECS335).</string>
    <string name="ECS336">This stock is not in the purchased stock list of margin account. Please contact to MBKE\'s Online-Trading Department (ECS336).</string>
    <string name="ECS337">Margin account can not sell this stock (ECS337).</string>
    <string name="ECS338">The system is temporarily unavailable. Please try again later (ECS338).</string>
    <string name="ECS339">Special account. Please contact MBKE (ECS339).</string>
    <string name="ECS34">You should change your Password and PIN code (ECS034).</string>
    <string name="ECS340">Customer using Tn payment service. Please contact MBKE (ECS340).</string>
    <string name="ECS341">Account under margin warning status. Please contact MBKE (ECS341). </string>
    <string name="ECS342">Amount withdrawal exceeds daily limit. Please contact MBKE (ECS342).</string>
    <string name="ECS343">Amount withdrawal must be multiple of hundred Dongs. Please try again (ECS343).</string>
    <string name="ECS344">You have not permission change order (ECS344).</string>
    <string name="ECS345">You have not authorized change order (ECS345).</string>
    <string name="ECS346">You can not change this order when it have cancelled (ECS346).</string>
    <string name="ECS347">You can not change this order when it have matched (ECS347).</string>
    <string name="ECS348">You can not change this order when it have rejected (ECS348).</string>
    <string name="ECS349">You can not cancel order that have waiting matching on SEC. When market status in break time (ECS349).</string>
    <string name="ECS35">The account was existed (ECS035).</string>
    <string name="ECS350">Do not allow to change HOSE\'s orders (ECS350).</string>
    <string name="ECS351">Do not allow to change HNX\'s orders (ECS351).</string>
    <string name="ECS352">Do not allow to change UPCOM\'s orders (ECS352).</string>
    <string name="ECS353">You might not have permission to use this channel. Please contact our Customer Service. (ECS353).</string>
    <string name="ECS354">Have no delegate permission to view information of requesting money for buying stock (ECS354).</string>
    <string name="ECS355">Have no delegate permission to change information of requesting money for buying stock (ECS355).</string>
    <string name="ECS356">Have no right to view information of requesting money for buying stock (ECS356).</string>
    <string name="ECS357">Have no right to change information of requesting money for buying stock  (ECS357).</string>
    <string name="ECS358">Do not allow to request money for buying stock which over orders value (ECS358).</string>
    <string name="ECS359">Do not allow to request money for buying stock with this account\'s type (ECS359).</string>
    <string name="ECS36">The agent is not exist (ECS036).</string>
    <string name="ECS360">Do not allow to request money for buying stock with the margin account (ECS360).</string>
    <string name="ECS361">Do not allow to pay money which is over the current balance (ECS361).</string>
    <string name="ECS362">Do not allow to pay money which is over EE (ECS362).</string>
    <string name="ECS363">You can register only one order at the same time. Currently, you have a pending/processing order (ECS363).</string>
    <string name="ECS364">The contract number is wrong. (ECS364).</string>
    <string name="ECS365">Could not cancel this order. (ECS365).</string>
    <string name="ECS367">You can not registered paid support when have not registered support (ECS367).</string>
    <string name="ECS368">Do not allow to pay over the registration of capital supporting (ECS368).</string>
    <string name="ECS37">Your session is expired or kicked out(ECS037).</string>
    <string name="ECS4">There are errors while sending email (ECS004).</string>
    <string name="ECS5">Can not logout (ECS005).</string>
    <string name="ECS500">@string/ECS3</string>
    <string name="ECS501">PIN  code is incorrect (ECS501).</string>
    <string name="ECS502">Update default account is unsuccessful (ECS502).</string>
    <string name="ECS503">Can not connect to database (ECS503).</string>
    <string name="ECS504">The old password is incorrect (ECS504).</string>
    <string name="ECS505">Password is not blank (ECS505).</string>
    <string name="ECS506">Something is wrong in email system (ECS506). Please contact Online Trading Department to get the detail instruction.</string>
    <string name="ECS507">PIN code is not blank (ECS507).</string>
    <string name="ECS508">Old PIN code is incorrect (ECS508).</string>
    <string name="ECS509">This account is not activated (ECS509).</string>
    <string name="ECS510">Can\'t put night order in this time (ECS510).</string>
    <string name="ECS511">This account is locked (ECS511).</string>
    <string name="ECS511_">The amount transferred is less than {0} VND(ECS511).</string>
    <string name="ECS512">The amount transferred is larger than {0} VND(ECS512).</string>
    <string name="ECS513">The system is not ready for night order (ECS513).</string>
    <string name="ECS514">You can not order ATO/MP/ATC price before trading time (ECS514).</string>
    <string name="ECS517">Your request of odd-lot selling of {0} can not be implemented currently. Please contact MBKE Contact Center (84&#8211;8) 38386636 for more details. Thank you! (ECS517).</string>
    <string name="ECS518">Unable to send SMS to this account (ECS518).</string>
    <string name="ECS519">Newsletter service received is not actived (ECS519).</string>
    <string name="ECS521">The MP order is not allowed in break time (ECS521).</string>
    <string name="ECS522">The stock transfer Qty must be bigger than zero (ECS522).</string>
    <string name="ECS523">Changed unsuccessfully. Please try again later (ECS523).</string>
    <string name="ECS524">Cancel unsuccessfully. Please try again later (ECS524).</string>
    <string name="ECS525">The effect date is not begin by saturday,sunday and holiday (ECS525).</string>
    <string name="ECS526">You are not allowed to view CC Information (ECS526).</string>
    <string name="ECS527">You are not allowed to change CC Information (ECS527).</string>
    <string name="ECS528">You are not allowed to view newsletter (ECS528).</string>
    <string name="ECS529">You are not allowed to register/update newsletter (ECS529).</string>
    <string name="ECS530">You have no delegated permission to view information on Online Trading services registration (ECS530).</string>
    <string name="ECS531">You have no delegated permission to change information on Online Trading services registration (ECS531).</string>
    <string name="ECS532">Wrong Qty, Qty must be greater than 0 (ECS532).</string>
    <string name="ECS533">You have not authorization to view newsletters (ECS533).</string>
    <string name="ECS534">You have not authorization to register/update newsletters services (ECS534).</string>
    <string name="ECS535">The symbol existed in your favorite category (ECS535).</string>
    <string name="ECS536">Due to problem on sending dynamic PIN to your email and sms. Please logout and login again for re-send it (ECS536).</string>
    <string name="ECS537">Do not exist bank account (ECS537).</string>
    <string name="ECS538">Do not allow to order MTL (ECS538).</string>
    <string name="ECS539">MTL is only valid in Cont. Session (ECS539).</string>
    <string name="ECS540">MAK is only valid in Cont. Session (ECS540).</string>
    <string name="ECS541">MOK is only valid in Cont. Session (ECS541).</string>
    <string name="ECS542">OBO is only valid in Cont. Session (ECS542).</string>
    <string name="ECS543">SBO is only valid in Cont. Session (ECS543).</string>
    <string name="ECS544">IO is only valid in Cont. Session (ECS544).</string>
    <string name="ECS545">SO> is only valid in Cont. Session (ECS545).</string>
    <string name="ECS546">SO&lt; is only valid in Cont. Session (ECS546).</string>
    <string name="ECS547">PLO is only valid in Cont. Session (ECS547).</string>
    <string name="ECS548">Do not allow to change order in this session (ECS548).</string>
    <string name="ECS549">This order does not allow in current session (ECS549).</string>
    <string name="ECS550">Do not allow to cancel or change order in this time (ECS550).</string>
    <string name="ECS551">This account does not exist in auto approve list (ECS551).</string>
    <string name="ECS552">The symbol does not exist (ECS552).</string>
    <string name="ECS553">The status of symbol does not allow to add order (ECS553).</string>
    <string name="ECS554">The status of symbol does not allow to cancel order (ECS554).</string>
    <string name="ECS555">Only allow to submit request to transfer money (withdrawn by EE) in trading time (ECS555).</string>
    <string name="ECS556">The symbol does not allow to trade in this time (ECS556)</string>
    <string name="ECS557">Don\'t allow to change this order (ECS557)</string>
    <string name="ECS558">Don\'t allow to change symbol in this session (ECS558)</string>
    <string name="ECS559">Don\'t allow to change side in this session (ECS559)</string>
    <string name="ECS560">Don\'t allow to change symbol (ECS560)</string>
    <string name="ECS561">Don\'t allow to change side (ECS561)</string>
    <string name="ECS562">Don\'t allow to change side so the order is put different session (ECS562)</string>
    <string name="ECS563">Don\'t allow to change symbol so the order is put different session (ECS563)</string>
    <string name="ECS564">Don\'t allow to change account (ECS564)</string>
    <string name="ECS565">Don\'t allow to change account in this session (ECS565)</string>
    <string name="ECS566">Don\'t allow to change order (ECS566)</string>
    <string name="ECS567">The symbol doesn\'t exists in symbol list of account (ECS567)</string>
    <string name="ECS568">Broker account does not have permission to trade on this channel (ECS568).</string>
    <string name="ECS569">Broker account does not have permission to do cash trade on this channel (ECS569).</string>
    <string name="ECS570">Broker account does not have permission to do stock trade on this channel (ECS570).</string>
    <string name="ECS571">Self agent does not have permission to trade on this channel (ECS571).</string>
    <string name="ECS572">Self agent does not have permission to do cash trade on this channel (ECS572).</string>
    <string name="ECS573">Self agent does not have permission to do stock trade on this channel (ECS573).</string>
    <string name="ECS574">You do not have permission to view Sign Online (ECS574).</string>
    <string name="ECS575">You do not have permission to register Sign Online (ECS575).</string>
    <string name="ECS576">You should change password because of more 6 months (ECS576)</string>
    <string name="ECS577">You should change pin because of more 6 months (ECS577)</string>
    <string name="ECS578">You should change password and pin because of more 6 months (ECS578)</string>
    <string name="ECS579">The symbol does not exist in margin stock list (ECS579)</string>
    <string name="ECS580">Your sell order is over limit of one sell order (ECS580).</string>
    <string name="ECS581">Your buy order is over limit of one buy order (ECS581).</string>
    <string name="ECS582">Broker does not have permission to view trade on this channel (ECS582).</string>
    <string name="ECS583">Broker does not have permission to view cash trade on this channel (ECS583).</string>
    <string name="ECS584">Broker does not have permission to view stock trade on this channel (ECS584).</string>
    <string name="ECS585">Self agent does not have permission to trade on this channel (ECS585).</string>
    <string name="ECS586">Self agent does not have permission to do cash trade on this channel (ECS586).</string>
    <string name="ECS587">Self agent does not have permission to do stock trade on this channel (ECS587).</string>
    <string name="ECS588">Broker does not have permission to view for this account (ECS588).</string>
    <string name="ECS589">Broker does not have permission to manipulate for this account (ECS589).</string>
    <string name="ECS590">Broker does not have permission to view account information on this channel (ECS590).</string>
    <string name="ECS591">Self agent does not have permission to view account information on this channel (ECS591).</string>
    <string name="ECS592">Broker does not have permission to change account information on this channel (ECS592).</string>
    <string name="ECS593">Self agent does not have permission to change account information on this channel (ECS593).</string>
    <string name="ECS594">Price is invalid (ECS594).</string>
    <string name="ECS595">Not allow to change price that is difference LO (ECS595).</string>
    <string name="ECS596">You do not have permission to view order confirmation (ECS596).</string>
    <string name="ECS597">You do not have permission to change order confirmation (ECS597).</string>
    <string name="ECS598">You do not have permission to view basket order (ECS598).</string>
    <string name="ECS599">You do not have permission to change basket order (ECS599).</string>
    <string name="ECS600">You do not have permission Chat (ECS600).</string>
    <string name="ECS601">You do not have authorization to view order confirmation (ECS601).</string>
    <string name="ECS602">You do not have authorization to change order confirmation (ECS602).</string>
    <string name="ECS603">You do not have authorization to view basket order (ECS603).</string>
    <string name="ECS604">You do not have authorization to change basket order (ECS604).</string>
    <string name="ECS605">The default branch code must be 01 (ECS605).</string>
    <string name="ECS606">Can not get the min money (ECS606).</string>
    <string name="ECS607">Can not get access config info (ECS607).</string>
    <string name="ECS608">(ECS608)</string>
    <string name="ECS609">Can not save system log (ECS609).</string>
    <string name="ECS610">Only allow to cancel order that has status into queue (00) (ECS610).</string>
    <string name="ECS611">Can not get stock account number from reference number (ECS611).</string>
    <string name="ECS612">Can not get bank info from bank code (ECS612).</string>
    <string name="ECS613">Only allow to update order that has status 00 (into queue) (ECS613).</string>
    <string name="ECS614">Cannot call web service. Please come later (ECS614)</string>
    <string name="ECS615">Can not transfer the money (ECS615).</string>
    <string name="ECS616">Can not get the cash balance (ECS616).</string>
    <string name="ECS630">{0} is non marginable securities. You can not buy it. Please contact broker for more detail (ECS630)!</string>
    <string name="ECS631">This basket order name is existed (ECS631)</string>
    <string name="ECS632">{0} is non marginable securities. It must be 100% funded by the investor\'s own cash, if not, VPBS will force sell the stock. Please contact broker for more detail (ECS632)!</string>
    <string name="ECS637">Password must have a minimum of %1$d characters, maximum of %2$d characters (ECS637)</string>
    <string name="ECS638">PIN code must have a minimum of %1$d characters, maximum of %2$d characters (ECS638)</string>
    <string name="ECS639">Please enter the password/PIN code with characters 0&#8211;9 or a&#8211;z or A&#8211;Z or [~!@#$%^&amp;*()_+|] and no white space (ECS639).</string>
    <string name="ECS641">The new password must be difference the old password (ECS641)</string>
    <string name="ECS642">The new PIN code must be difference the old PIN code (ECS642)</string>
    <string name="ECS643">The channel is invalid (ECS643)</string>
    <string name="ECS644">Warning: You are wrong over %1$s times on authentication. (ECS644)</string>
    <string name="ECS645">Error: You are wrong over %1$s times on authentication. Please wait for %2$s seconds to continue. (ECS645)</string>
    <string name="ECS646">Currently, the system can not send sms/email (ECS646)</string>
    <string name="ECS667">The authenticated code has expired (ECS667)</string>
    <string name="ECS717">The captcha is required to confirm (ECS717)</string>
    <string name="ECS6">Your token is incorrect (ECS006).</string>
    <string name="ECS7">Invalid secret question (ECS007).</string>
    <string name="ECS8">Invalid secret answer (ECS008).</string>
    <string name="ECS82">Reject from core stock (ECS82).</string>
    <string name="ECS9">Your session is error. Please login again (ECS009).</string>
    <string name="ECS900">Don\'t have enough cash balance or EER to trade (ECS900).</string>
    <string name="ECS901">The symbol doesn\'t exist in list that is allowed to buy by credit limit (ECS901).</string>
    <string name="ECS902">The orders value is greater than value that is allowed to buy by credit limit (ECS902).</string>
    <string name="ECS903">The orders value is greater than allowing limit (ECS903).</string>
    <string name="ECS904">The symbol is occupied more than 50 percent the portfolio value of margin account (ECS904).</string>
    <string name="ECS905">Don\'t have enough cash balance or EER to trade (ECS905).</string>
    <string name="ECS999">MBKE suspends the orders using power purchase in Credit contract with bank over KE Trade. Please contact Brokers for place orders (ECS999).</string>
    <string name="ECS97">Transaction suspended from %1$s to %2$s (ECS097)</string>
    <string name="ECSPlus2">System error. Cannot connect to server (ECS002).</string>
    <string name="ECS718">@string/ECS3</string>
    <string name="ECS719">The captcha is expired (ECS719)</string>
    <string name="ECS722">You do not have permission to view Gifts Information (ECS722)</string>
    <string name="ECS723">You do not have permission to view Loyalty Point (ECS723)</string>
    <string name="ECS724">You do not have permission to Change Gift (ECS724)</string>
    <string name="ECS640">The customer has to register this agreement feature (ECS640)</string>
    <string name="ECS790">Condition information is not correct. Please check. (ECS790)</string>
    <string name="ECS794">Can not place PLO order when symbol has not had matched Qty (ECS794)</string>
    <string name="ECS805">The registered verification id (Personal ID, Passport, Company Code ID) is incorrect (ECS805).</string>
    <string name="ECS806">You have not registered channel to receive notice (ECS806)</string>
    <string name="ECS807">You must be register device to receives OTP if you choose notification channel in OTP service (ECS807)</string>
    <string name="ECS808">The query duration (from date, to date) must be less than 30 days. (ECS808)</string>
    <string name="ECS809">Query time is too far from current day (ECS809)</string>
    <string name="ECS810">Your device type already registered, please cancel to create new registration (ECS810)</string>
    <string name="ECS812" tools:ignore="ExtraTranslation">Account has been changed type authentication, please login again. (ECS812)</string>
    <string name="ECS813">Please update device to receive OTP (ECS813)</string>
    <string name="ECS804">The confirmation code was expired (ECS804)</string>
    <string name="ECS789">Effective time is invalid (ECS789)</string>
    <string name="ECS772">The Utility perform into time from %1$s to %2$s (ECS772)</string>
    <string name="ECS776">Orders trigger price is not smaller than or equal to last price. (ECS776)</string>
    <string name="ECS825">Your favorite is existed (ECS825)</string>
    <string name="ECS826">Your account is using certificate authentication. Please login on your computer to continue using (ECS826)</string>
    <string name="ECS1032">The amount transferred in day is larger than %1$s VND (ECS1032)</string>
    <string name="ECS1033">You are using (or change to) OTP authentication, so you must choose once notification channel of authentication service (OTP) (ECS1033)</string>
    <string name="ECS1034">The changing orders must be changed at least one field. (ECS1034)</string>
    <string name="ECS1035">Wrong volume, volume must be less than maximum order volume can buy/sell (ECS1035)</string>
    <string name="ECS1038">Your session is not used. Please re-login (ECS1038) </string>
    <string name="ECS1039">Not allow to place this price in this session (ECS1039)</string>
    <string name="ECS1041">You need OTP code for Two - Factor Authentication (ECS1041)</string>
    <string name="ECS1042">Please re-register mobile to receive OTP. Please contact to {0} E-Trading Department (ECS1042)</string>
    <string name="ECS1044">Can not connect to market data (ECS1044)</string>
    <string name="ECS1045">Customer has been actived. Cannot re-active (ECS1045)</string>
    <string name="ECS1046">Please don\'t input special charater(ECS1046)</string>
    <string name="ECS1047">Order action is unsuccessful (ECS1047)</string>
    <string name="ECS1050">You have not withdraw permission at MO (ECS1050)</string>
    <string name="ECS1051">From %1$s to %2$s (GMT+7), HSC systems are processing day-end data. Your portfolio information maybe inaccurate for the time being. Please revisit later. Thank you.</string>
    <string name="ECS1051_Login">From %1$s to %2$s (GMT+7), HSC systems are processing day-end data. Your portfolio information maybe inaccurate for the time being. Please revisit later. Thank you.</string>
    <string name="ECS1057">You can not choose services that not allow to selectable  (ECS1057)</string>
    <string name="ECS1062">The confirmation code is invalidated after [5] failed attempts. Please request a new one (ECS1062)</string>
    <string name="ECS1067">The feature does not match with feature code in the authentranstion id (ECS1067)</string>
    <string name="ECS1068">Margin Account is not allowed to register for odd-lot selling. Please transfer odd-lot shares to Cash Account to register (ECS1068)</string>
    <string name="ECS1069">Your ID card is reaching expired date. Please contact our company to update your ID prior to registering for odd-lot selling (ECS1069)</string>
    <string name="ECS1094">Not support to place odd lot order in this session (ECS1094)</string>
    <string name="ECS1113">Error Favourite Name over max length (ECS1113)</string>
    <string name="ECS1095">Error handling transaction fee when transfer to a registered bank (ECS1095)</string>
    <string name="ECS697">Your confirmation code is locked now, please contact trading department  (ECS697)</string>
    <string name="ECS2000">Cannot transfer orderinfo to Core(ECS2000)</string>
    <string name="ECS1110">The login device is different from the one registered to receive OTP. Would you like to re-register?(ECS1110)</string>
    <string name="ECS1116">The market is temporarily halting trading (ECS1116)</string>
    <string name="ECS1117">Not support to place odd lot order for special range symbol (ECS117)</string>
    <string name="ECS1118">Can not change/cancel order for halt symbol  in last session PCA (ECS1118)</string>
    <string name="ECS1119">Can not change both volume and price (ECS1119)</string>
    <string name="ECS1120">Not support to place order in this session (ECS1120)</string>
    <string name="ECS1121">Not support to place order with condition price in this session (ECS1121)</string>
    <string name="ECS1122">Not support to place order with halt PCA in this session (ECS1122)</string>
    <string name="ECS1123">Please wait in 3 minutes for resend OTP (ECS1123)</string>
    <string name="ECS1124">The OTP authentication is temporary locked. Please try again in %1$s minutes or contact CS at 1900 633 996 for assistance (ECS1124)</string>
    <string name="ECS1135">Not support to place odd lot for PCA status symbol (ECS1135)</string>
    <string name="ECS1137">Error authen order 2FA (ECS1137)</string>
    <string name="ECS1143">Halt symbol can not order with market price in this session (ECS1143)</string>
    <string name="ECS1147">Account has confirmed registration (ECS1147)</string>
    <string name="ECS5078">The email already exists in the system. Please enter a different email. (ECS5078)</string>
    <string name="ECS5079">The phone number already exists in the system. Please enter a different phone number. (ECS5079)</string>
    <string name="ECS5080">Your IdentityCard was existed (ECS5080).</string>
    <string name="ECS5184">You are not old enough to open an account(ECS5184)</string>
    <string name="ECS5185">Your IdentityCard is invalid (ECS5185).</string>

    <string name="RCC0">MP order without contra-side (RCC000).</string>
    <string name="RCC1">Illegal price spread. (RCC001)</string>
    <string name="RCC2">Incorrect Qty for specified board. (RCC002)</string>
    <string name="RCC3">Illegal request - Market Closed. (RCC003)</string>
    <string name="RCC4">Incorrect Stock Symbol. (RCC004)</string>
    <string name="RCC5">Incorrect Firm. (RCC005)</string>
    <string name="RCC6">Incorrect Trader ID. (RCC006)</string>
    <string name="RCC7">Incorrect confirm number. (RCC007)</string>
    <string name="RCC8">Too late to perform requested action. (RCC008)</string>
    <string name="RCC9">Incorrect Reference Number. (RCC009)</string>
    <string name="RCC10">Incorrect Conditions. (RCC010)</string>
    <string name="RCC11">Trading halted in Stock. (RCC011)</string>
    <string name="RCC12">Incorrect Board. (RCC012)</string>
    <string name="RCC13">Wait for connecting to core stock system (RCC013)</string>
    <string name="RCC14">Incorrect Order Type. (RCC014)</string>
    <string name="RCC15">Incorrect Port / Client flag. (RCC015)</string>
    <string name="RCC16">Incorrect PIN Code. (RCC016)</string>
    <string name="RCC17">Error connection. (RCC017)</string>
    <string name="RCC18">Incorrect Order Number. (RCC018)</string>
    <string name="RCC19">Incorrect Time. (RCC019)</string>
    <string name="RCC20">Incorrect Date. (RCC020)</string>
    <string name="RCC21">Cannot do on Odd-Lot board. (RCC021)</string>
    <string name="RCC22">Incorrect Sub-Broker ID. (RCC022)</string>
    <string name="RCC23">Illegal Trustee ID. (RCC023)</string>
    <string name="RCC24">Security suspended. (RCC024)</string>
    <string name="RCC25">Missing P/C Flag. (RCC025)</string>
    <string name="RCC26">Missing Sub-Broker ID. (RCC026)</string>
    <string name="RCC27">No available room for foreign investor. (RCC027)</string>
    <string name="RCC28">Market in Intermission. (RCC028)</string>
    <string name="RCC29">Market Halted. (RCC029)</string>
    <string name="RCC30">Incorrect Published Qty. (RCC030)</string>
    <string name="RCC31">Changing Deal information disallowed. (RCC031)</string>
    <string name="RCC32">Publish Qty disallowed at this time. (RCC032)</string>
    <string name="RCC33">Trading disallowed for this stock. (RCC033)</string>
    <string name="RCC34">Incorrect price - above ceiling. (RCC034)</string>
    <string name="RCC35">Incorrect price - below floor. (RCC035)</string>
    <string name="RCC36">Put-Through price incorrect format. (RCC036)</string>
    <string name="RCC37">Cancel of automatch deal disallowed. (RCC037)</string>
    <string name="RCC38">Incorrect Qty for Put-Through deal. (RCC038)</string>
    <string name="RCC39">Incorrect Market Maker. (RCC039)</string>
    <string name="RCC40">Illegal Short Sales Order. (RCC040)</string>
    <string name="RCC41">Illegal Market ID. (RCC041)</string>
    <string name="RCC42">Illegal Message Type/Header. (RCC042)</string>
    <string name="RCC43">Illegal Message Length. (RCC043)</string>
    <string name="RCC71">Warning! Price over 10 %. (RCC071)</string>
    <string name="RCC81">Disapprove Order. (RCC081)</string>
     <string name="RCC82">Reject from the core securities system (RCC082)</string>
    <string name="RCC97">Trading is halted. (RCC097)</string>
    <string name="RCC98">Reject by Authorize Teller or System (RCC098)</string>
    <string name="RCC99">Unidentified Error. (RCC099)</string>
    <string name="RCC100">Symbol is halted in normal session. (RCC100)</string>
    <string name="RCC101">Symbol is halted in put-through session. (RCC101)</string>
    <string name="RCC200">Invalid account. (RCC200)</string>
    <string name="RCC201">Account don\'t active. (RCC201)</string>
    <string name="RCC202">Customer can not buy margin order. (RCC202)</string>
    <string name="RCC203">Customer can not buy order. (RCC203)</string>
    <string name="RCC204">Customer can not sell pledge order. (RCC204)</string>
    <string name="RCC205">Customer can not sell order. (RCC205)</string>
    <string name="RCC206">Customer can not sell lending order. (RCC206)</string>
    <string name="RCC207">Order SBL isn\'t support. (RCC207)</string>
    <string name="RCC208">Credit type can\'t use SBL. (RCC208)</string>
    <string name="RCC209">Account foreign stock replace normal stock. (RCC209)</string>
    <string name="RCC210">Account can\'t short sell. (RCC210)</string>
    <string name="RCC211">Over limit value per order. (RCC211)</string>
    <string name="RCC212">Can\'t new order Order Qty Exeed Control Qty. (RCC212)</string>
    <string name="RCC213">Account can\'t buy stock. (RCC213)</string>
    <string name="RCC214">Account can\'t sell stock. (RCC214)</string>
    <string name="RCC215">Stock can\'t buy. (RCC215)</string>
    <string name="RCC216">Stock can\'t sell. (RCC216)</string>
    <string name="RCC217">Stock can\'t short lending. (RCC217)</string>
    <string name="RCC218">Account cannot short stock. (RCC218)</string>
    <string name="RCC219">Invalid account\'s broker. (RCC219)</string>
    <string name="RCC220">Invalid enterID. (RCC220)</string>
    <string name="RCC221">Trader id not active. (RCC221)</string>
    <string name="RCC222">Branch of trader should be branch id or zero. (RCC222)</string>
    <string name="RCC223">Order number is duplicate. (RCC223)</string>
    <string name="RCC224">Order over limit Qty, val. (RCC224)</string>
    <string name="RCC225">Invalid SDCAccID. (RCC225)</string>
    <string name="RCC226">Market link is down can\'t send order. (RCC226)</string>
    <string name="RCC227">No Pos type can\'t send SBL order. (RCC227)</string>
    <string name="RCC228">Not found Positions. (RCC228)</string>
    <string name="RCC229">Return error from routine credit. (RCC229)</string>
    <string name="RCC230">Update control Qty array fail. (RCC230)</string>
    <string name="RCC231">Exist sell order,SDC ACC cannot buy order. (RCC231)</string>
    <string name="RCC232">Exist buy order,SDC ACC cannot sell order. (RCC232)</string>
    <string name="RCC233">Account have lending can\'t Buy/Sell. (RCC233)</string>
    <string name="RCC234">Over stock loan, Qty limit. (RCC234)</string>
    <string name="RCC235">Over account loan limit. (RCC235)</string>
    <string name="RCC236">Over broker loan limit. (RCC236)</string>
    <string name="RCC237">Over company advance. (RCC237)</string>
    <string name="RCC238">Invalid session for ATC price. (RCC238)</string>
    <string name="RCC239">Trader can\'t key ATC price. (RCC239)</string>
    <string name="RCC240">OrdVol &lt; ATC min Qty. (RCC240)</string>
    <string name="RCC241">Invalid session for MP price. (RCC241)</string>
    <string name="RCC242">Trader can\'t key MP price. (RCC242)</string>
    <string name="RCC243">OrdVol &lt; MP min Qty. (RCC243)</string>
    <string name="RCC244">Over cash. (RCC244)</string>
    <string name="RCC245">Not enough money for buying (RCC245).</string>
    <string name="RCC246">Account can\'t short Qty. (RCC246)</string>
    <string name="RCC247">Insert ordno is fail. (RCC247)</string>
    <string name="RCC251">Window full can’t send order, waiting for message confirm order from Stock Exchange (RCC251)</string>
    <string name="RCC300">Market status is intermission, you can\'t cancel order. (RCC300)</string>
    <string name="RCC301">Invalid cancelID. (RCC301)</string>
    <string name="RCC302">Invalid order status. (RCC302)</string>
    <string name="RCC303">Invalid Side to cancel 1-Firm Order. (RCC303)</string>
    <string name="RCC304">Locking state, cancel fail. (RCC304)</string>
    <string name="RCC305">Waiting rekey state, cancel order is fail. (RCC305)</string>
    <string name="RCC306">You cannot cancel in this session. (RCC306)</string>
    <string name="RCC307">Market link is down can\'t cancel order. (RCC307)</string>
    <string name="RCC308">Return error from routine credit. (RCC308)</string>
    <string name="RCC309">Update ordno fail. (RCC309)</string>
    <string name="RCC400">Invalid ordno. (RCC400)</string>
    <string name="RCC401">Change order was failed because market disallow change account. (RCC401)</string>
    <string name="RCC402">The change is fail, order isn\'t waiting state. (RCC402)</string>
    <string name="RCC403">disallow change HoseTP to non-Hose. (RCC403)</string>
    <string name="RCC404">disallow change non-Hose to HoseTP. (RCC404)</string>
    <string name="RCC405">Disallow change diffrence market mode. (RCC405)</string>
    <string name="RCC406">No fields to change. (RCC406)</string>
    <string name="RCC407">Invalid session for ATC price. (RCC407)</string>
    <string name="RCC408">You can\'t change order because trader can\'t key ATC price. (RCC408)</string>
    <string name="RCC409">You can\'t change order because order Qty &lt; ATC min Qty. (RCC409)</string>
    <string name="RCC410">You can\'t change order because session is invalid for MP price. (RCC410)</string>
    <string name="RCC411">You can\'t change order because trader can\'t key MP price. (RCC411)</string>
    <string name="RCC412">You can\'t change order because order Qty &lt; MP min Qty. (RCC412)</string>
    <string name="RCC413">Orders have been locked by trader. (RCC413)</string>
    <string name="RCC414">Trader can\'t change order. (RCC414)</string>
    <string name="RCC415">Invalid old account. (RCC415)</string>
    <string name="RCC416">Invalid new account. (RCC416)</string>
    <string name="RCC417">Order cannot change account. (RCC417)</string>
    <string name="RCC418">Order cannot change account sell only. (RCC418)</string>
    <string name="RCC419">Order will margin short sell. (RCC419)</string>
    <string name="RCC420">Order will short sell. (RCC420)</string>
    <string name="RCC421">Order status is invalid. (RCC421)</string>
    <string name="RCC422">You can\'t change same customer id. (RCC422)</string>
    <string name="RCC423">Only change to same SDC. (RCC423)</string>
    <string name="RCC424">The change is fail because Order is locking state. (RCC424)</string>
    <string name="RCC425">The change is fail because Order is waiting rekey state. (RCC425)</string>
    <string name="RCC426">Update order fail for new customer id. (RCC426)</string>
    <string name="RCC500">Order already match can not change. (RCC500)</string>
    <string name="RCC501">Order Invalid Qty. (RCC501)</string>
    <string name="RCC502">Order cancel is confirm late, you cannot change price. (RCC502)</string>
    <string name="RCC503">Broker link down: cannot change publish to set. (RCC503)</string>
    <string name="RCC504">Market status cannot change publish to set. (RCC504)</string>
    <string name="RCC505">Broker link down: cannot change account to set. (RCC505)</string>
    <string name="RCC506">Market status can\'t change account to set. (RCC506)</string>
    <string name="RCC507">Market Link is down can\'t send advertise. (RCC507)</string>
    <string name="RCC508">Order received broker confirm, Cancelled not complete. (RCC508)</string>
    <string name="RCC509">Broker confirm cancel order in put-through session: Return error from routine credit. (RCC509)</string>
    <string name="RCC510">Broker confirm cancel order in put-through session: Update control Qty array is fail. (RCC510)</string>
    <string name="RCC511">Invalid ordon. (RCC511)</string>
    <string name="RCC512">Order is invalid status to change price. (RCC512)</string>
    <string name="RCC513">You can\'t change order because session is invalid for ATC price. (RCC513)</string>
    <string name="RCC514">You can\'t change order because trader can\'t key ATC price. (RCC514)</string>
    <string name="RCC515">You can\'t change order because order Qty &lt; ATC min Qty. (RCC515)</string>
    <string name="RCC516">You can\'t change order because session is invalid for MP price. (RCC516)</string>
    <string name="RCC517">You can\'t change order because trader can\'t key MP price. (RCC517)</string>
    <string name="RCC518">You can\'t change order because order Qty &lt;MP min Qty. (RCC518)</string>
    <string name="RCC519">Order duplicate change price, last change isn\'t done. (RCC519)</string>
    <string name="RCC520">Invalid Order No. (RCC520)</string>
    <string name="RCC521">You can\'t update order. (RCC521)</string>
    <string name="RCC522">Order change price process is time out. (RCC522)</string>
    <!-- <string name="RCC255">Over cash (RCC255)</string> -->
    <string name="RCC600">Can\'t new order/Invalid symbol (RCC600)</string>
    <string name="RCC601">Can\'t change/can\'t create msg queue (RCC601)</string>
    <string name="RCC602">Can\'t change/order no not available (RCC602)</string>
    <string name="RCC603">Can\'t change/full match (RCC603)</string>
    <string name="RCC604">Can\'t change price/invalid market stock (RCC604)</string>
    <string name="RCC605">Can\'t change/no detail, not response from serve (RCC605)</string>
    <string name="RCC700">Invalid ord status (RCC700)</string>
    <string name="RCC701">Ord has been approved (RCC701)</string>
    <string name="RCC702">Ord has been disapproved (RCC702)</string>
    <string name="RCC703">Invalid approve_id (RCC703)</string>
    <string name="RCC704">Invalid account (RCC704)</string>
    <string name="RCC705">Credit unavail for approval ordno (RCC705)</string>
    <string name="RCC706">TID can\'t approve or disapprove ord_no (RCC706)</string>
    <string name="RCC707">Order Need Approve by ID (RCC707)</string>
    <string name="RCC708">Invalid approve code (can be only A or D) (RCC708)</string>
    <string name="RCC082">REJECT FROM HNX (New,Cancel,Change) (RCC082)</string>
    <string name="RCC432">Market Status is Close BL.Can‟t change order (RCC432)</string>
    <string name="RCC255">Error Lv3 : Duplicated Orders Continuous (RCC255)</string>
    <string name="RCC256">Error Lv3 : Duplicated Orders Discontinuous (RCC256)</string>
    <string name="RCC2000">The core system is upgrading. Please come back in a few hours (RCC2000)</string>

    <string name="ECI001">Market is closed (ECI001)</string>
    <string name="ECI002">Stock cannot be blank (ECI002).</string>
    <string name="ECI003">Qty cannot be blank (ECI003).</string>
    <string name="ECI004">Price cannot be blank (ECI004).</string>
    <string name="ECI006">Price is invalid (ECI006).</string>
    <string name="ECI007">Invalid Qty (ECI007).</string>
    <string name="ECI008">The price is not greater than ceiling price (ECI008).</string>
    <string name="ECI009">The price is not lower than floor price (ECI009).</string>
    <string name="ECI010">Incorrect instrument code, please try again. In case new listed instrument, information will be updated after receiving from the Exchange (ECI010)</string>
    <string name="ECI013">Wrong Qty, Qty must be multiples of lot %1$s (ECI013).</string>
    <string name="ECI014">Wrong Qty, Qty must be multiples of lot 10 (ECI014).</string>
    <string name="ECI015">Wrong Qty, Qty must be &lt;= %1$s (ECI015).</string>
    <string name="ECI016">Wrong Qty, the Qty must be &lt;= %1$s (ECI016).</string>
    <string name="ECI017">Wrong Qty, Qty must be less than stock balance (ECI017).</string>
<!--    <string name="ECI018">Not enough money for buying (ECI018).</string>-->
    <string name="ECI020">Qty must be greater than 0 (ECI020).</string>
    <string name="ECI021">Price is incorrect: It is multiply by 100 for HNX stock (ECI021).</string>
    <string name="ECI022">Price is incorrect: It is multiply by 100 for HOSE stock (in case Price  50,000) (ECI022).</string>
    <string name="ECI023">Price is incorrect: It is multiply by 500 for HOSE stock (in case 50,000 &lt;= Price &lt; 100,000) (ECI023).</string>
    <string name="ECI024">Price is incorrect: It is multiply by 1,000 for HOSE stock (in case Price &gt;= 100,000) (ECI024).</string>
    <string name="ECI025">Price is incorrect: No ATO, ATC, MP for HNX market (ECI025).</string>
    <string name="ECI026">Price is incorrect: ATO is only valid in Ready &amp; ATO Session (ECI026).</string>
    <string name="ECI027">Price is incorrect: ATC is only valid in ATC Session (ECI027).</string>
    <string name="ECI028">Market is going to the Cont. Session. No ATO order is accepted (ECI028).</string>
    <string name="ECI030">Market is in the Put Through session. No order is accepted (ECI030).</string>
    <string name="ECI035">Please enter the old password (ECI035).</string>
    <string name="ECI036">Please enter the new password (ECI036).</string>
    <string name="ECI037">Please enter the verify password (ECI037).</string>
    <string name="ECI038">New password and verify password is not the same (ECI038).</string>
    <string name="ECI039">Please enter security code (ECI039).</string>
    <string name="ECI041">Please enter Customer ID (ECI041).</string>
    <string name="ECI042">Please enter password (ECI042).</string>
    <string name="ECI055">Please enter the old PIN code (ECI055).</string>
    <string name="ECI056">Please enter the new PIN code (ECI056).</string>
    <string name="ECI057">Please enter the verify new PIN code (ECI057).</string>
    <string name="ECI058">The new PIN code and verify PIN code is not the same (ECI058).</string>
    <string name="ECI063">Cannot connect to server (ECI063).</string>
    <string name="ECI064">The system is processing. Please check the status.</string>
    <string name="ECI166">You don\'t have this stock in your portfolio (ECI166).</string>
    <string name="ECI226">Price is incorrect: No ATO, ATC or MP for UPCOM market (ECI226)</string>
    <string name="ECI227">Wrong Qty, the Qty must be greater %1$s (ECI227).</string>
    <string name="ECI229">Invalid account (ECI229).</string>
    <string name="ECI230">Account No cannot be blank (ECI230).</string>
    <string name="ECI231">Price is incorrect: MP is only valid in Cont. Session (ECI231)</string>
    <string name="ECI231KRX">Price is incorrect: MTL is only valid in Cont. Session (ECI231)</string>
    <string name="ECI232">Please enter only characters 0&#8211;9 or a&#8211;z or A&#8211;Z or [~!@#$%^&amp;*()_+|] and white space (ECI232).</string>
    <string name="ECI233">Password must have a minimum of %1$d characters, maximum of %2$d characters (ECI233).</string>
    <string name="ECI240">Please, enter your cash advance request (ECI240).</string>
    <string name="ECI242">The amount exceeds Max withdrawable Amount (ECI242).</string>
    <string name="ECI243">The amount exceeds remaining daily transfer limit.</string>
    <string name="ECI244">Bank name not empty (ECI244).</string>
    <string name="ECI245">City name is required (ECI245)</string>
    <string name="ECI246">Money not empty (ECI246).</string>
    <string name="ECI249">Begin date is invalid (ECI249).</string>
    <string name="ECI251">Begin date is bigger than end date (ECI251).</string>
    <string name="ECI253">End date is invalid (ECI253).</string>
    <string name="ECI290">Unidentify error (ECI290).</string>
    <string name="ECI264">Your favorite is existed (ECI264).</string>
    <string name="ECI265">The Contact Address cannot be blank (ECI265).</string>
    <string name="ECI268">Cellphone number can not be blank (ECI268).</string>
    <string name="ECI272">The Email Address cannot be blank (ECI272).</string>
    <string name="ECI273">Error! Cellphone number is invalid (ECI273).</string>
    <string name="ECI283">New PIN Code and verify PIN code is not the same (ECI283).</string>
    <string name="ECI301">The transfer amount incorrect (ECI301).</string>
    <string name="ECI302">Volume must not be greater than buyable volume (ECI302).</string>
    <string name="ECI305">The volume can not be null (ECI305)</string>
    <string name="ECI310">Number of orders is invalid (ECI310).</string>
    <string name="ECI312">Step price is invalid. Please reduce the number of orders or the step price (ECI312).</string>
    <string name="ECI316">Qty for sending can not be greater than available Qty (ECI316).</string>
    <string name="ECI319">You must select at least one order (ECI319).</string>
    <string name="ECI322">You have to register at least one alert condition (ECI322).</string>
    <string name="ECI328">Invalid new name (ECI328).</string>
    <string name="ECI341">You do not have a margin account so this function is disabled (ECI341).</string>
    <string name="ECI342">You do not have a normal account so this function is disabled (ECI342).</string>
    <string name="ECI345">You have not enough cash. Pls, view your total amount (ECI345).</string>
    <string name="ECI355">Choose order to cancel (ECI355).</string>
    <string name="ECI360">You must enter the percent greater than 0 and less than or equal to 100 (ECI360)</string>
    <string name="ECI361">Absolute cannot be blank (ECI361)</string>
    <string name="ECI362">Absolute must be greater than 0 (ECI362)</string>
    <string name="ECI363">Percent cannot be blank (ECI363)</string>
    <string name="ECI364">Absoluted-value interval could not be blank (ECI364)</string>
    <string name="ECI365">Absoluted-value interval is not valid (ECI365).</string>
    <string name="ECI367">Percentage-vale interval is not valid (ECI367).</string>
    <string name="ECI373">The Effective date must more than or equal current date (ECI373).</string>
    <string name="ECI374">Expired date (To Date) of the conditional command orders shall not exceed %1$s days (ECI374).</string>
    <string name="ECI380">You just view data in %1$s months (ECI380).</string>
    <string name="ECI381">The end date must not be greater than current date (ECI381).</string>
    <string name="ECI382">The effect date is not begin by saturday,sunday and holiday (ECI382).</string>
    <string name="ECI391">Email format is incorrect (ECI391)</string>
    <string name="ECI396">Wrong Qty, Qty must be greater than 0 (ECI396).</string>
    <string name="ECI397">The step Qty must be multiples of 10 (ECI397).</string>
    <string name="ECI398">The step Qty must be multiples of %1$s (ECI398).</string>
    <string name="ECI400">You cannot buy the stock volume equal to or less than 0 (ECI400).</string>
    <string name="ECI403">You should select the take profit or stop loss (ECI403).</string>
    <string name="ECI404">You may not place more than %1$s orders in an order group/split order (ECI404).</string>
    <string name="ECI406">The Effective date must less than or equal %1$s days from the current date (ECI406)</string>
    <string name="ECI407">OTP can not be empty (ECI407).</string>
    <string name="ECI409">This order is expired. Please select an effective date starting from the next trading day (ECI409).</string>
    <string name="ECI4111">Do not support this order type (ECI411)</string>
    <string name="ECI412">Only order MOK in Cont. Session (ECI412).</string>
    <string name="ECI413">Only order MAK in Cont. Session (ECI413).</string>
    <string name="ECI414">Only order MTL in Cont. Session (ECI414).</string>
    <string name="ECI419">The amount transferred is not larger than %1$s VND (ECI419).</string>
    <string name="ECI420">The amount transferred is not larger than %1$s VND (ECI420).</string>
    <string name="ECI422">Please enter your confirm code (ECI422)</string>
    <string name="ECI426">The cash advanced value is less than %1$s VND (ECI426).</string>
    <string name="ECI428">The changing orders must be changed at least one field (ECI428).</string>
    <string name="ECI429">Branch name not empty (ECI429).</string>
    <string name="ECI430">Cannot add more stock. It is over %1$s (ECI430)</string>
    <string name="ECI431">PIN code must have a minimum of %1$d characters, maximum of %2$d characters (ECI431).</string>
    <string name="ECI435">You may not place more than {0} orders in an order split (ECI435)</string>
    <string name="ECI439">Wrong volume, volume must be less than Mortage balance (ECI439)</string>
    <string name="ECI441">The price step is incorrect  (ECI441)</string>
    <string name="ECI442">The range of price from %1$s to %2$s, must have price step is %3$s (ECI442)</string>
    <string name="ECI443">Price is incorrect: In case Price >= %1$s VND, the step price must be %2$s VND(ECI443)</string>
    <string name="ECI444">You should select the Up Trend or Down Trend  (ECI444)</string>
    <string name="ECI447">Cannot change order because its Qty is in different lots (ECI447)</string>
    <string name="ECI448">The change order volume must be greater than matched volume (ECI448)</string>
    <string name="ECI497">The order price is invalid in this session (ECI497)</string>
    <string name="ECI433">The new password must be difference the old password (ECI433)</string>
    <string name="ECI445">Trigger price is invalid (ECI445)</string>
    <string name="ECI459">Please choose symbol to transfer (ECI459)</string>
    <string name="ECI466">You have no order in basket (ECI466)</string>
    <string name="ECI495">Your device type already registered, please cancel to create new registration (ECI495)</string>
    <string name="ECI434">The new PIN code must be difference the old PIN code (ECI434)</string>
    <string name="ECI494">Please re-check and you want to send more request (ECI494)?</string>
    <string name="ECI453">Series cannot be blank (ECI453).</string>
    <string name="ECI455">Choose positions to close (ECI455)</string>
    <string name="ECI506">Wrong quantity, quantity must be less than maximum order quantity can buy/sell (ECI506)</string>
    <string name="ECI509">No orders have been placed (ECI509)</string>
    <string name="ECI522">Not enough money or purchase power for buying  (ECI522)</string>
    <string name="ECI532">Trigger price cannot be blank (ECI532)</string>
    <string name="ECI533">This condition order only support for Short not for Long order (ECI533)</string>
    <string name="ECI535">This condition order only support for Long not for Short order (ECI535)</string>
    <string name="ECI537">Loss price cannot be blanked (ECI537)</string>
    <string name="ECI538">Loss price is invalid (ECI538)</string>
    <string name="ECI540">Trigger price / Cut Loss price does not allow Condition Price (ECI540)</string>
    <string name="ECI541">Adjusted price = Loss price - Spreed = %1$s must be >= Floor price = %2$s (ECI541)</string>
    <string name="ECI542">Adjusted price =  Loss price + Spreed = %1$s must be &lt;= Ceiling price = %2$s (ECI542)</string>
    <string name="ECI543">Loss price must be &lt; Last price = %1$s (ECI543)</string>
    <string name="ECI544">Loss price must be > Last price = %1$s (ECI544)</string>
    <string name="ECI546">Profit price = Order price + Profit step = %1$s must be &lt;= Ceiling price = %2$s (ECI546)</string>
    <string name="ECI547">Adjusted price = Order price - Loss step - Spread = %1$s must be >= Floor price = %2$s (ECI547)</string>
    <string name="ECI548">Profit price = Order price - Profit step = %1$s must be >= Floor price = %2$s (ECI548)</string>
    <string name="ECI549">Adjusted price = Order price - Loss step - Spread = %1$s must be &lt;= Ceiling price = %2$s (ECI549)</string>
    <string name="ECI550">Adjusted price = Order price + Loss step + Spread = %1$s must be >= Floor price = %2$s (ECI550)</string>
    <string name="ECI551">Adjusted price = Order price + Loss step + Spread = %1$s must be &lt;= Ceiling price = %2$s (ECI551)</string>
    <string name="ECI556">You just view data in %1$s days (ECI556)</string>
    <string name="ECI701">The registered verification id (Personal ID, Passport, Company Code ID) cannot be blank (ECI701).</string>
    <string name="ECI775">Trigger price must be &lt; Last price = %1$s (ECI775)</string>
    <string name="ECI776">Trigger price must be > Last price = %1$s (ECI776)</string>
    <string name="ECI774">Trigger time must be between %1$s and %2$s (ECI774)</string>
    <string name="ECI778">Basket name cannot be blank (ECI778)</string>
    <string name="ECI782">Trigger price must be &lt;= Ceiling price = %1$s (ECI782)</string>
    <string name="ECI783">Trigger price must be &gt;= Floor price = %1$s (ECI783)</string>
    <string name="ECI785">Condition orders does not allow Condition Price (ECI785)</string>
    <string name="ECI772">The Utility perform into time from %1$s to %2$s (ECI772)</string>
    <string name="ECI784">Please input Conditional order information (ECI784)</string>
    <string name="ECI786">Order price must be &lt; Last price = %1$s (ECI786)</string>
    <string name="ECI787">Order price must be > Last price = %1$s (ECI787)</string>
    <string name="ECI789">Profit Step / Loss Step is invalid (ECI789)</string>
    <string name="ECI790">Loss price must be difference Order price (ECI790)</string>
    <string name="ECI815">The spread is invalid (ECI815)</string>
    <string name="ECI465">You may not place more than {0} orders in an basket order. (ECI465)</string>
    <string name="ECI458">The symbol is not enough room (ECI458)</string>
    <string name="ECI529">Not enough money or purchase power for selling (ECI529)</string>
    <string name="ECI440">Volume of GroupOrder Must be greater than %1$s (ECI440)</string>
    <string name="ECI830">Transaction suspended from %1$s to %2$s (ECI830)</string>
    <string name="ECI861">Please enter Bank Account (ECI861)</string>
    <string name="ECI862">Please enter Bank and Branch (ECI862)</string>
    <string name="ECI863">Please enter Province / City (ECI863)</string>
    <string name="ECITemp3">Please select stock symbol</string>
    <string name="ECI888">The password must include:\nMust be At least 4 characters\nHave at least one of the characters: [~!@#$%^&amp;*?>&lt;]\nMust have at least 1 uppercase letter (A - Z)\nMust have at least 1 lowercase letter (a - z)\nMust have at least 1 number (0 - 9)</string>
    <string name="ECI889">The pin must include:\nMust be At least 4 characters\nHave at least one of the characters: [~!@#$%^&amp;*?>&lt;]\nMust have at least 1 uppercase letter (A - Z)\nMust have at least 1 lowercase letter (a - z)\nMust have at least 1 number (0 - 9)</string>
    <string name="ECI893">You are under {0} years old to open an account. Please contact Customer Service (+84)24 3248 4820 for further instructions. (ECI893)</string>
    <string name="ECI905">Please select a bank from the suggested list (ECI905)</string>
    <string name="ECI906">Broker information does not exist. (ECI906)</string>
    <string name="ECI960">Can not change both Price and Quantity (ECI960)</string>
    <string name="ECI968">Please enter only characters 0–9 or a-z or A-Z, length not exceed 1000 characters</string>
    <string name="mts_mt_eci_max_min" />
    <string name="ECS803">Please get OTP code again after you receive last OTP code for at least %1$d seconds (ECS803)</string>
    <string name="ECS1063">The OTP code is incorrect. Please try again (ECS1063)</string>
    <string name="ECS1109">Fail to register sOTP cause device token not found</string>
    <string name="ECS1156">Approval failed.</string>
    <string name="ECS1157">The PIN/Smart PIN for your account has been changed. Please re-login!</string>
    <string name="ECS1158">The repayment amount must not exceed the Total amount. (ECS1158)</string>
    <string name="ECS1162">Exceeded the number of OTP requests, please re-login to continue request. (ECS1162)</string>

</resources>
